Raymond, Eleanor. The Eleanor Raymond Collection: An Inventory.
Eleanor Raymond Collection.
- Series E / Eleanor Raymond Addendum, E000
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), : E021; / Quantity: 2 / Medium: film
Peck, Charles R. (client) / Design development drawings A5111
Peck, Russell (client) / Blueprints A5103
Peck (client) / Details A5507
Pereira, Felix (client) / Correspondence A6807
Perkins (client) / Construction drawings A7001
Perkins (client) / Design development drawings A7101
Phillips, Mr. & Mrs. William A. (client) / Construction drawings A6901
Phipps, Helen (landscape architect) / Design development drawings A5002
Pinney, Charlotte (client) / Construction drawings A3522
Podren (client) / Design development drawings A5310
Pope, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph (client) / Blueprints A4911
Pope, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph (client) / Correspondence A5617
Pope, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph (client) / Project files A5701
Potter, Mrs. John (client) / Photographs C012
Power, Dorothy M. (client) / Correspondence A5906
Power, Dorothy M. (client) / Design development drawings A424, A4902
Power, Dorothy M. (client) / Interior perspectives A453
Power, Dorothy M. (client) / Measured drawings A4410, A4610
Power, Dorothy M. (client) / Project files A4612
Power, Ethel (author) / Books B014
Power, Ethel (diarist) / Diaries D003, D004, D005
Power, Ethel (photographer) / Photographs D010
Preston, Mrs. Roger (client) / Correspondence A6608, A6709
Preston, Philip (client) / Correspondence A7002
Rafferty, Dr. Brae (client) / Clippings A6003
Raymond, Eleanor, 1887-1989 / Professional papers (Collection)
Raymond, Eleanor (architect) / Professional papers (Collection)
Raymond, Eleanor (author) / Books B012, B013
Raymond, Eleanor (compiler) / Notebooks B019, B020, B021
Raymond, Eleanor (owner) / Articles B006
Raymond, Eleanor (photographer) / Albums D006
Raymond, Eleanor (student) / Albums D006
Raymond, Rachel (photographer) / Albums D007
Raymond, T.E. (client) / Correspondence A5801
Raymond (client) / Correspondence A6109
Reinert (Reinhart?) (client) / Construction drawings A6511
Reynolds (client) / Correspondence A5709
Richardson (client) / Correspondence A6506
Richardson (client) / Project files A5114
Robinson (client) / Design development drawings A5105
Roy, L.C. (collaborating architect) / Clippings A5606
Roy, L.C. (draftsman) / Bids A6101
Rust (client) / Project files A4708
Sargent (client) / Construction drawings A6902
Schroeder, Mrs. Eric (client) / Contracts A5409
Schroeder, Mrs. Eric (client) / Correspondence A6213
Scott, David C. (client) / Project files A4018
Sears (previous owner) / Correspondence A5905
Shattuck (client) / Blueprints A4616
Sibley (client) / Correspondence A5711
Simonds (client) / Correspondence A5801
Singer (client) / Correspondence A6310
Smith, Horace Hale (client) / Project files A4210
Smith, Mary Byers (client) / Blueprints A4518
Smith, Mary Byers (client) / Construction drawings A3610, A6710
Smith, Mary Byers (client) / Correspondence A6804
Smith, Mary Byers (client) / Diazo process prints A6605
Smith, Mary Byers (client) / Notes A6708
Smith, Mary Byers (client) / Photographs C010
Smith-Petersen (client) / Project files A5325
Smith-Taylor (client) / Brochures A6810
Spencer, Duncan (client) / Construction drawings A7306
Stackpole, Mrs. M.W. (client) / Construction drawings A4809
Stackpole, Mrs. M.W. (client) / Measured drawings A4522
Staples (client) / Correspondence A5813
Stevens, David (client) / Correspondence A6404
Stevens (client) / Invoices A5915
Stoneman (client) / Correspondence A6309
Storey (client) / Correspondence A6509, A6514
Storrs (client) / Correspondence A5914
Story, Anne (client) / Project files A7009
Strock (client) / Correspondence A7004
Sugarman, Bertram A. (client) / Construction drawings A3511
Taintor (client) / Correspondence A5302
Taplin (client) / Construction drawings A7205
Taves, Mrs. Ernest (client) / Construction drawings A6501
Taves, Mrs. Ernest (client) / Cuts A7308
Taves, Mrs. Judith de F. (client) / Appeals A6803
Telkes, Maria (solar consultant) / Clippings A4802
Telkes, Maria (solar consultant) / Project files A4210
Thayer, Mrs. James B. (client) / Sketches A412
Thompson (client) / Correspondence A6112
Thoron (client) / Correspondence A6308
Tolnan (client) / Correspondence A5901
Vaitses, Mr. & Mrs. Theodore (client) / Clippings A5613
Vaitses, Mr. & Mrs. Theodore (client) / Correspondence A5923, A5924, A6002
Van Wyck (client) / Contracts A5510
von Mertens, Hartold (client) / Construction drawings A6903
Walworth (client) / Project files A4806
Ward, Sam (client) / Diazo process prints A7502
Warner (client) / Contracts A5101
Watson (client) / Clippings A5705
Weber, Paul J. (photographer) / Photographs C012
Weld (client) / Contracts A6305
Wellman (client) / Design development drawings A5205
White (client) / Correspondence A6205
Whiting (client) / Design development drawings A5002
Whitnack, Jean (client) / Correspondence A6507
Whitnack, Jean (client) / Notes A7012
Wigglesworth, Mrs. William (client) / Correspondence A6004
Wigglesworth, Richard B. (client) / Construction drawings A3611
Wigglesworth (client) / Design development drawings A5607
Wile, Henry E. (builder ?) / Blueprints A386
Wile, Henry E. (builder) / Correspondence A6515
Wile, Henry E. (client) / Blueprints A4014
Wile, Henry E. (client) / Construction drawings A4412
Wile, Henry E. (client) / Correspondence A6609
Wile, Henry E. (client) / Project files A4618
Wile, Henry E. (contractor) / Blueprints A456
Wilkenson (client) / Certificates A6508
Williams, B. (client) / Blueprints A4614
Williams, H.D.H. (client) / Construction drawings A4511
Williams, Mr. & Mrs. John (client) / Cuts A7302
Winchester (client) / Contracts A6403
Wolfe (client) / Cuts A7304
Wood (client) / Design development drawings A454
Woodward (client) / Diazo process prints A5418
Woolsey (client) / Correspondence A6208
Wright (client) / Project files A5404
Corporate Names Index
Adden, Parker, Clinch & Crimp (architects (collab.)) / Correspondence A5108
Beckman Pool (client) / Measured drawings A7501
Braeburn Club (client) / Correspondence A5904
Butler (pre-fabricator) / Plot plans A5218
Copley Society (client) / Project files A5907
Crotched Mountain Rehabilitation (client) / Correspondence A5108
Davis, George (photographer) / Construction drawings A343
Deck House (pre-fabricator) / Project files A6402
Dover Church (client) / Bids A5916
Dover Church (client) / Correspondence A5925
E.F. Hodgson Co. (pre-fabricator) / Diazo process prints A5210
Exolite (manufacturer) / Construction drawings A5812
F.H.A., Washington, D.C. (client) / Blueprints A4921
Frost & Raymond (architects) / Construction drawings A2912, A333, A343, A3511, A3515, A3516, A353, A359
Frost House / Photographs E009
Frost House / Slides E013, E019
Hammond Compound / Photographs E001, E005, E006
Hammond Compound / Slides E016
Haskell (photographer) / Construction drawings A416
High Spruces / Slides E015
Ipswich School / Clippings A6206
Irvine House / Slides E018
Irvine House (addition) / Photographs E004
Kikwood, Grace (landscape architects) / Correspondence A5910
Lord & Burnham Greenhouses (manufacturer) / Correspondence A6506
Massachusetts General Hospital (client) / Project files A5618
Miller House / Photographs E003
N.E. Erecting Co. (contractor) / Plot plans A5218
Nichols Factory / Photographs E010
Nichols Factory / Slides E018
Nudor Sliding Doors (manufacturer) / Contracts A5505
Old North Church (client) / Clippings A5810
Old South Church (client) / Correspondence A6515
Olmsted Brothers (landscape architects) / Clippings A6104, A6106
Orchard School (client) / Design development drawings A5107
Parker, Stanley (architects) / Correspondence A5702
Parker House / Photographs E002
Parker House / Slides E015, E020
Parkwood (manufacturer) / Project files A5304
Parsons, Ester (associate architect) / Photographs C001
Peabody Studio / Slides E014
Perrin, Helen Baxter (associate architect) / Photographs C001
Phillips, E.L. & Holloran, T.F. (architects) / Blueprints A5015
Power Ltd. (client) / Correspondence A5911
Power Ltd. (client) / Design development drawings A4902
Power Ltd. (client) / Project files A4612, A5106
Rachel Raymond House / Photographs E007
Randall, Rex (estimator) / Correspondence A5914
Ravenswood Cove Chapel (client) / Blueprints A5515
Raymond's Summer House / Slides E012
Resolite (manufacturer) / Correspondence A5910
Resolite (manufacturer) / Project files A5304
Resolite Roofing (manufacturer) / Design development drawings A5301
Sayre (photographer) / Photographs C001
St. Peter's Church (client) / Photostats A5309
Stone, Fred (photographer) / Blueprints A4911
Sun House / Slides E015
Techbilt (pre-fabricator) / Brochures A6810
Textolite (manufacturer) / Contracts A5505
Theodore Miller House / Slides E014
Timber Structures (contractor) / Photostats A5309
TZE House (client) / Photographs C008
Union Pacific Railroad (owner) / Cuts A7308
Vaughan's Studio (photographer) / Blueprints A4911
W.H. Nichols & Company (client) / Addenda A5917
Waites Motor Company (previous owner) / Correspondence A6007
Walpole Fence (manufacturer) / Design development drawings A5301
Wascolite Skydome (manufacturer) / Construction drawings A5601
Wayside Inn (client) / Clippings A5606
Weber, Paul J. (photographer) / Photographs C001
Wellesley College / Albums D006
Westville (pre-fabricator) / Brochures A7206
Wilson-Cole Corporation (fabricator) / Correspondence A5608
WKNE (client) / Blueprints A4908
Wolfers Lighting (distributor) / Project files A5605
YWCA (client) / Correspondence A5909
Titles Index
Early Domestic Architecture of Pennsylvania / Books B012, B013
LC Topical Headings Index
Architecture, Modern -- 20th century -- United States / Professional papers (Collection)
Carpentry / Clippings A5810
Carpentry / Correspondence A5617
Carpets / Addenda A5917
Lighting, architectural and decorative / Addenda A5917
Women architects -- United States / Professional papers (Collection)
Geographic Names Index
::: Alexander Kitchen Remodeling / Invoices A6503
::: Bowditch House Alterations / Diazo process prints A6301
::: Brennan Garden Plan / Project files A4611
::: Brookings / Project files A7402
::: Danforth Cottage Alterations / Contracts A5704
::: Douglas Kitchen Remodeling / Project files A4530
::: Dunsford House Renovations / Project files A4623
::: Farnsworth Addition / Correspondence A5703
::: Fuller Remodeling / Correspondence A5811
::: Jordan House Alterations / Correspondence A6812
::: MacInnis Residential Projects / Measured drawings A4512
::: McClelland Barn Apartment / Correspondence A5814
::: McGreal House Alterations / Blueprints A5706
::: Miller House Remodeling / Design development drawings A5417
::: Munn House Interior Renovations / Project files A4615
::: Peabody Miscellaneous / Correspondence A5919
::: Perkins House Alterations / Design development drawings A7101
::: Story Project / Project files A7009
::: Thayer House Renovation / Sketches A412
::: Vaitses House Alterations / Clippings A5613
::: Watson Residence / Clippings A5705
::: Whitnack Project / Notes A7012
Arizona: Oracle: Vaitses House / Correspondence A5924
Arizona: Oracle: Vaitses Project / Correspondence A6002
Connecticut: Chaplin: Rafferty House Alterations / Clippings A6003
Connecticut: Fairfield: Phillips House Addition / Construction drawings A6901
Connecticut: Groton: Ellis Garage / Correspondence A6204
Connecticut: Haddam: Ellis House / Articles B003
Connecticut: Haddam: High Spruces / Photographs C005
Connecticut: High Spruces / Slides E015
Connecticut: Roxbury: Brookings Kitchen Remodeling / Construction drawings A7003
Connecticut: Sharon: Blewer House / Cuts A7202
Connecticut: Sharon: Blewer House Alterations / Invoices A7204
Florida: Inverness: Ellis House / Brochures A7303
Idaho: Aberdeen: Union Pacific Station Project / Cuts A7308
Iowa:: Charlotte Pinney House / Construction drawings A3522
Maine: Bailey Island: Adams Barracks / Blueprints A4704
Maine: Biddeford Pool: Harrison House Alterations / Project files A5519
Maine: Biddeford Pool: Legg Sun Room Alteration / Photographs A5518
Maine: Biddeford Pool: Smith House / Construction drawings A6710
Maine: Biddeford Pool: Smith House Addition / Project files A4210
Maine: Biddeford Pool: Smith House Alterations / Diazo process prints A6605
Maine: Biddeford Pool: Smith House Alterations / Notes A6708
Maine: Biddeford Pool: Stackpole House Addition / Measured drawings A4522
Maine: Camden: Bowditch House / Project files A6402
Maine: Camden: Bowditch House Library / Correspondence A5702
Maine: Hancock Point: Dickerson House / Construction drawings A4715
Maine: North Haven: Ketchum House / Correspondence A6304
Maryland: Kent County: du Pont House / Photographs C001
Massachusetts:: Apple House Apartment Renovation / Construction drawings A389
Massachusetts:: Gun Club Cottage Addition / Project files A387
Massachusetts:: Mitchell Studio / Articles B011
Massachusetts:: Peabody "Herdsman" Cottage / Negatives A4414
Massachusetts:: Power Interior Alterations / Measured drawings A4610
Massachusetts: Andover: Smith, Mary Byers House / Articles B007
Massachusetts: Andover: Smith House / Articles B007
Massachusetts: Ashby: Farnsworth (Marion B.) Projects / Construction drawings A3516
Massachusetts: Ashby: Farnsworth Blue Gates Renovation / Project files A417
Massachusetts: Ashby: Farnsworth Orchard Cottage / Measured drawings A5412
Massachusetts: Ashby: Moulton House / Project files A5115
Massachusetts: Ashby: Wright House Alterations / Project files A5404
Massachusetts: Belmont: Babcock House Alterations / Correspondence A6103
Massachusetts: Belmont: Churchill House / Clippings A6104
Massachusetts: Belmont: Irvine House / Bids A6312
Massachusetts: Belmont: Irvine House / Photographs E008
Massachusetts: Belmont: Johannet Landscaping / Landscape plans A5402
Massachusetts: Belmont: Markham House / Correspondence A6510
Massachusetts: Belmont: Massachusetts / Slides E018
Massachusetts: Belmont: McCreary House / Construction drawings A5616
Massachusetts: Belmont: Meyer House / Construction drawings A5614
Massachusetts: Belmont: Miller, Theodore T. / Construction drawings A365
Massachusetts: Belmont: Rachel Raymond House / Photographs C007
Massachusetts: Belmont: Simonds House Alterations / Correspondence A5801
Massachusetts: Belmont: White House Alterations / Correspondence A6205
Massachusetts: Belmont: Whiting House / Design development drawings A5002
Massachusetts: Beverly: Doriot House / Notes A5019
Massachusetts: Beverly: Weld House Alterations / Contracts A6305
Massachusetts: Boston / Scrapbooks C014
Massachusetts: Boston: 112 Charles Street House / Photographs C004, C006
Massachusetts: Boston: Anderson Renovation / Design development drawings A4605
Massachusetts: Boston: Anderson Townhouse Remodeling / Project files A458
Massachusetts: Boston: Barnes Townhouse Renovation / Blueline prints A4517
Massachusetts: Boston: Bowditch Townhouse Renovation / Correspondence A6001
Massachusetts: Boston: Bowman Townhouse Conversion / Diazo process prints A5503
Massachusetts: Boston: Copley Society Project / Project files A5907
Massachusetts: Boston: Crosby Townhouse Renovation / Blueprints A456
Massachusetts: Boston: Cushman & Sears House Remodeling / Correspondence A5905
Massachusetts: Boston: Dexter House Alterations / Correspondence A5921
Massachusetts: Boston: Farnsworth Projects / Correspondence A5804
Massachusetts: Boston: Gardiner Townhouse Alteration / Correspondence A5608
Massachusetts: Boston: Grote Townhouse Alterations / Correspondence A7006
Massachusetts: Boston: Henry Landscape Project / Correspondence A5908
Massachusetts: Boston: Jacobson Apartment / Clippings A5802
Massachusetts: Boston: Jenny Townhouse Renovation / Project files A5902
Massachusetts: Boston: M.G.H., Out-Patient Department / Project files A5618
Massachusetts: Boston: MacLeish Garden / Project files A4920
Massachusetts: Boston: Manville House Alteration / Project files A5605
Massachusetts: Boston: Old North Church, Rector's Study / Clippings A5810
Massachusetts: Boston: Old South Church Projects / Correspondence A6515
Massachusetts: Boston: Peabody Exhibition / Correspondence A6712
Massachusetts: Boston: Peabody Garage / Project files A4811
Massachusetts: Boston: Peabody Kitchen Alteration / Diazo process prints A4711
Massachusetts: Boston: Peabody Pool / Cuts A7208
Massachusetts: Boston: Peabody Projects (Commonwealth Ave.) / Construction drawings A3515
Massachusetts: Boston: Penthouse Addition to Townhouse / Design development drawings A5105
Massachusetts: Boston: Pope-Shaw Kitchen Renovation / Correspondence A5617
Massachusetts: Boston: Potter Garden / Photographs C012
Massachusetts: Boston: Power Ltd. Exhibits / Project files A5106
Massachusetts: Boston: Power Ltd. Projects / Design development drawings A4902
Massachusetts: Boston: Raymond Office / Articles B006
Massachusetts: Boston: Singer Townhouse Renovation / Correspondence A6310
Massachusetts: Boston: Smith Townhouse Alterations / Correspondence A6804
Massachusetts: Boston: Smith Townhouse Renovation / Blueprints A4518
Massachusetts: Boston: Stoneman Kitchen Alterations / Correspondence A6309
Massachusetts: Boston: Thoron House Interior Alterations / Correspondence A6308
Massachusetts: Boston: YWCA Remodeling / Correspondence A5909
Massachusetts: Brewster: Ballantine House / Project files A4311
Massachusetts: Brockton: Horowitz House Alterations / Correspondence A6214
Massachusetts: Brookline: Alden House Alterations / Correspondence A6701
Massachusetts: Brookline: Bowditch House Alterations / Correspondence A6111
Massachusetts: Brookline: Braeburn Club Remodeling / Correspondence A5904
Massachusetts: Brookline: Haskell Garden Plan / Correspondence A6212
Massachusetts: Brookline: Hubbard House Alteration / Contracts A6703
Massachusetts: Brookline: Hubbard House Alteration / Correspondence A5922
Massachusetts: Brookline: Olmsted House / Construction drawings A376
Massachusetts: Brookline: Olmsted Supt.'s House Alterations / Correspondence A6604
Massachusetts: Brookline: Paine House Alterations / Measured drawings A5018
Massachusetts: Brookline: Simon Project / Invoices A7010
Massachusetts: Brookline: Sugarman House / Construction drawings A3511
Massachusetts: Cambridge / Diaries D001, D002
Massachusetts: Cambridge / Manuscripts B017
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Bowditch House Addition / Design development drawings A5301
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Chase Kitchen Alterations / Correspondence A6307
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Frost House / Outline specifications A3518
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Frost House / Photographs E009
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Frost House / Slides E019
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Greene House Addition / Project files A5304
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Gring House Addition / Appeals A6502
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Lennihan House / Articles B010
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Longfellow Park / Project files A5304
Massachusetts: Cambridge: McClelland Project / Correspondence A5911
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Morgan Kitchen Remodeling / Clippings A5926
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Morse House Renovations / Project files A4617
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Peck House Remodeling / Blueprints A5103
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Power Webster House Alterations / Project files A4612
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Taves Garage Addition / Appeals A6803
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Taves House Addition / Construction drawings A6501
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Thompson House Alterations / Correspondence A6112
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Woolsey Garden Projects / Correspondence A6208
Massachusetts: Canton: Bradley House Alterations / Correspondence A6806
Massachusetts: Charlemont: Parker Farmhouse Alterations / Project files A4914
Massachusetts: Chestnut Hill: Crosby House Alterations / Cuts A7503
Massachusetts: Chestnut Hill: Jackson House / Articles B009
Massachusetts: Concord: Atkins Kitchen Alterations / Correspondence A6202
Massachusetts: Concord: Mason House / Blueline prints A4805
Massachusetts: Concord: The Retreat / Measured drawings A449
Massachusetts: Concord: Williams House / Construction drawings A4511
Massachusetts: Dedham: Conant House Alterations / Project files A4907
Massachusetts: Dover: Bradley House for Amelia Peabody / Construction drawings A364
Massachusetts: Dover: Children's Chapel at The Dover Church / Correspondence A5925
Massachusetts: Dover: Dover Church / Bids A5916
Massachusetts: Dover: Farm Group / Slides E019
Massachusetts: Dover: Farnsworth Projects (Exmoor Farm) / Construction drawings A395
Massachusetts: Dover: Otis Kitchen Remodeling / Invoices A6505
Massachusetts: Dover: Park Projects / Correspondence A6108
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody "Hodgson House" / Diazo process prints A5210
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody "Westville Sporthaus" / Brochures A7206
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Aluminum Barn & Projects / Plot plans A5218
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Barn Cottage Alteration / Project files A4702
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Border House / Construction drawings A4814
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody-Chase Projects / Correspondence A5610
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Dave's House / Correspondence A6113
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Deck House / Contracts A6813
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Garage Addition / Construction drawings A392
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Greenhouse (Mill Farm) / Construction drawings A359
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Pig House / Outline specifications A3311
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Plywood House / Construction drawings A404
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Projects / Construction drawings A3515
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Projects / Diazo process prints A5314
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Projects (Mill Farm) / Construction drawings A343
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Sculpture Studio (Mill Farm) / Construction drawings A333
Massachusetts: Dover: Peabody Sun-Heated House / Clippings A4802
Massachusetts: Dover: Sun House / Slides E015
Massachusetts: Duxbury: Brown House Alterations / Diazo process prints A7209
Massachusetts: Duxbury: Fitzgibbon Memorial / Correspondence A6702
Massachusetts: Duxbury: Fitzgibbon Renovations / Blueprints A4602
Massachusetts: East Brewster: Baxter-Ward Antique Shop / Correspondence A7005
Massachusetts: East Brewster: Baxter-Ward Speculative Housing / Invoices A7007
Massachusetts: East Brewster: Callahan House Alterations / Negatives A7104
Massachusetts: East Gloucester: Robinson Garage Cottage / Blueprints A5015
Massachusetts: Essex: Raymond Barn Renovation / Correspondence A6109
Massachusetts: Essex: Reinert House Addition / Construction drawings A6511
Massachusetts: Essex: Storey House Addition / Correspondence A6509
Massachusetts: Essex: Storey Well House / Correspondence A6514
Massachusetts: Falmouth: Kirkwood-Dupee Landscape Projects / Correspondence A5910
Massachusetts: Gloucester / Diaries D003, D004
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Blick Alterations Projects / Construction drawings A4629
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Buswell House Remodeling / Project files A444
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Coon House / Correspondence A5714
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Donovan House / Blueprints A5014
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Ellis House Alterations / Bids A6101
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Gloucester Red Cross / Measured drawings A4514
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Hammond Compound / Construction drawings A419
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Hammond Compound / Photographs E001, E005, E006
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Hammond Compound / Slides E016
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Howard Housing Development / Correspondence A5803
Massachusetts: Gloucester: Mussell Point House / Photographs C002
Massachusetts: Gloucester Ravenswood Cove Chapel / Blueprints A5515
Massachusetts: Groton: Memorial Seat to Groton Hunt / Correspondence A6512
Massachusetts: Haverhill: Barnes House Renovation / Construction drawings A2912
Massachusetts: Haverhill: Barnes House Renovation / Project files A442
Massachusetts: Haverhill: Barr House / Correspondence A5912